[

](https://moqups.com/ "Go to Moqups Homepage")

[

](#js-menu "Open navigation menu")

Privacy Policy
==============

**_Effective starting: May 22, 2018_**

What this policy covers
-----------------------

This updated Privacy Policy reflects Moqups’ commitments and obligations under the EU’s new General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).

Your privacy is important to us, so the goal of this policy is to be transparent about what information Moqups collects, uses, and shares.

This policy explains your rights with regards to that information. It also explains how to access and update your information, and how you can object to its use.

When we refer to “Moqups”, “we”, or “us”, we mean the Moqups entity (owned by S.C. Evercoder Software S.R.L.) that acts as the controller or processor of your information.

### This policy covers:

1. [What information we collect and how we use it](https://moqups.com/privacy/#collect)
2. [How we share information](https://moqups.com/privacy/#share)
3. [How we store, secure, and transfer information](https://moqups.com/privacy/#store)
4. [Your data rights and choices](https://moqups.com/privacy/#rights)
5. [List of data sub-processors](https://moqups.com/privacy/#subprocessors)
6. [Contacting Moqups](https://moqups.com/privacy/#contact)

When we make changes to our Privacy Policy, we will revise the date at the top of this page. We may also notify you via in-app messages or by email.

What information we collect and how we use it
---------------------------------------------

Moqups collects the following information about you when you provide it to us and use our services:

### Account and Profile Information

When you sign up, create a profile, set your preferences, or pay for your subscription, Moqups collects your name, username, password, email, address, company information, and any profile pictures or avatars you choose to upload.

> We use this information to correctly identify you, communicate with you, and provide you with customer support. We also use this contact information for accounting and administrative purposes, for transactional emails including app and billing notifications, and to notify you about new features, releases, blog posts, and discounts.

### User Created Content

As you work on your projects, Moqups stores the content you create, send, receive, and share. This includes any assets you upload to Moqups, such as images, icons, or logos. It also includes comments posted to your projects by you, your team members, and your collaborators.

> We use this information to securely store your work, and provide access to your team members and the collaborators you designate.

### Device Information and Log Data

We collect information about the type of device you use to access Moqups, as well as your device settings, operating system, browser information, connection type, IP address, and the URLs of referring pages. Additionally, we log the date and time you access our services, as well as any error or crash data.

> We use device and location information to help us optimize your Moqups’ display and performance, provide accurate billing information, understand user demographics, and improve overall user experience. Your log data helps us troubleshoot errors, analyze performance, resolve reliability issues, perform security audits, and investigate potential service fraud or abuse.

### Payment Information

Customers that purchase a paid Moqups subscription provide us, or our payment processors, with billing details such as credit or debit card information, banking information, and billing addresses. When you purchase a subscription through one of our payment processors, we receive only partial information about your card, and Moqups doesn’t store cardholder information on our servers.

> We use your payment information in order to fulfil, track, and manage your subscription.

### Service Metadata

This data is generated automatically, when you visit Moqups. It provides us with information about how you browse our website and use our app. That includes the links you click, the search terms you use, and the features you access.

> We use this metadata to help us understand how our users work, and what they find most valuable at Moqups. We also use this information to measure the efficiency of our product, enhance our services and guide our future development.

### Support Information

When you reach out to Moqups, you may contact our team through the service of a third-party support platform. The information you provide to our team, including any troubleshooting documentation or screen shots, are saved as part of your support history.

> We use this information to resolve any issues you are having, relay feedback to our team, respond to your comments and requests, and confirm your purchases and refunds. We also use this data to provide you with security alerts and technical notices.

### Cookie Information

Moqups and our third-party advertising and analytics partners use cookies and similar technologies for tracking across different devices, websites and online services.

> We use this information both for secure authentication and for the maintenance of your active sessions. Our third-party partners use cookies for the purposes of marketing, ad targeting, and performance analytics.

### Integrations and Linked Services

Moqups offers integrations with a number of third-party services. For instance, you can sign up and log into Moqups by using Google, Slack, and other third-party authentication providers. You can also connect your Moqups account to Google Drive and Dropbox in order to be able to export and save your projects there. We also offer add-ons to Atlassian’s Jira and Confluence platforms.

Whenever you or your account owner links to one of these third-party services, Moqups is authorized to connect and transfer information as specified by our agreement with that linked service.

> We use this information to authenticate, connect, or link your third-party accounts to Moqups. However, we do not receive or store passwords for any of these third-party services.

> To understand what data may be shared with Moqups when you enable these integrations, please check the settings, permissions and privacy policies of these third-party services.

### Information Provided by Other Users

Other Moqups users may provide contact information about you when they share content, or when they invite you to collaborate on a project.

> We use this information to facilitate collaboration, and to help you communicate with your team members and stakeholders.

How we share information
------------------------

### We Do Not Sell Your Information

Moqups users create and share sensitive and proprietary data on our platform. Since we appreciate our users’ need for privacy, we adhere to a straightforward business model based on the offer of both paid subscriptions and free plans. This means that, no matter what Moqups plan you choose, we will never sell information about you, your profile, your projects, nor your data and metadata, to advertising companies or other third parties.

### Other Moqups Users

Moqups is a collaborative platform that’s designed to let you share and disseminate your work. This means you are free to invite your peers to view, comment, download, or edit collaboratively in real time, depending on the settings that you select. You can also choose to make your work publically available. In addition, you may also grant your team members project access rights that are equivalent to yours, including the ability to transfer your project ownership to a different account. Some of these collaborative features display your publicly accessible profile information to the other users you’ve invited to collaborate.

### Community and Forums

Moqups offers publicly accessible blogs and community forums. Any comments you contribute to these platforms may be read, collected or used by any member of the public who chooses to access them. Your information may remain posted on these sites, even if your account is deleted at your request.

### Testimonials and Case Studies

We might contact you with a request to provide information that would appear, as a testimonial or case study, on our blog and website. In this case, we would seek explicit, written consent to use this information.

### Social Media Links and Third-Party Widgets

Some Moqups services include social media links and widgets. In order to function properly, these features may set a cookie that records the Moqups page from which you engaged them, as well as your IP address. These features may also link to other websites or services whose privacy policies differ from ours. As a result, any information you provide to them will be governed by their policies and not this one.

### Third-Party App Integrations

Moqups users are free to allow third-party apps and integrations to connect to their Moqups account. Once enabled, Moqups may share information with those services. Moqups does not control the way in which these services collect, share, or use information. Because of this, Moqups users should review the privacy policies of all third-party services before connecting to, or using their applications.

### Legal Compliance and Fraud Prevention

In exceptional circumstances, we may disclose information about you to a third party if we receive a request and believe that the disclosure is in accordance with or required by any applicable law, rule or regulation, legal process, or enforceable governmental request. We may also do so to enforce our Terms of Service, investigate potential violations, prevent and detect fraud, track and solve security or technical issues, and protect against any harm to the rights, property or safety of Moqups, its users, or the public as required or permitted by law.

### Changes in Business

If Moqups engages in a merger, acquisition, reorganization, bankruptcy, dissolution, sale of company assets, financing, public offering of securities, or due diligence and other steps in contemplation and negotiation of such activities, we may share or transfer information that we collect under this privacy policy, subject to standard confidentiality agreements.

How we store, secure, and transfer information
----------------------------------------------

### Third Party Service Providers

Moqups contracts with third party service providers. These services may require access to your information in order to help us operate, market, and support our services. For example, Moqups uses third party services to provide hosting, maintenance, backup, virtual computing, storage, payment processing, customer support, data analytics, advertising, marketing, and other services. Our contracts with these services provide for the maintenance, confidentiality, security, and integrity of the information we share with them.

### Data Security

Moqups takes data security very seriously and implements the industry’s best practices and policies. We take all reasonable measures to protect your information, and to prevent any kind of unauthorized access, misuse, loss, or disclosure.

The third-party service providers that we use for infrastructure and payment processing are ISO certified and PCI compliant, and they adhere to the same privacy and security principles as we do.

We conduct regular, manual and automated security audits. We also participate in voluntary penetration tests performed by third parties; these test are followed by concrete, internal security policy updates and actionable engineering items for our development team. When possible, your data is also stored in anonymised form.

While no system is infallible, we strive to keep our systems secure and constantly updated.

### Data Retention

Moqups stores your information for as long as your account is active, and for a reasonable period thereafter, in case you decide to use our services again. Moqups may also retain certain information for as long as necessary in order to support business operations, or as required by law.

### International Data Transfers

Moqups collects information internationally, and uses hosting and cloud computing infrastructure located primarily in the United States to transfer, process and store information. In order to provide you with our service, we may also transfer your data to third-party services. Please refer to the [List of data sub-processors](https://moqups.com/privacy/#subprocessors) for more information about why we use those third-party services, and where they are located.

Your data rights and choices
----------------------------

The following is a summary of choices you can make to exercise your data rights:

### Opt Out of Promotional Communications

You have the right to opt out of receiving any promotional communication. To unsubscribe from our newsletter, or other promotional emails, use the link at the bottom of the message. You can also contact us directly to have your information removed from our promotional contact list. Please note that, even if you unsubscribe, you will continue to receive non-promotional, transactional messages regarding your account and other essential services.

### Access and Update Personal Information

You have the right to access and edit your profile and billing information at any time. You also have the right to rectification in case your personal data is incomplete or inaccurate. To update your information, log in to your account and use the editing tools in your Moqups Dashboard. If you require assistance, please contact our Support team.

### Right to be Forgotten

You have the _right to be forgotten_ which means that, at any time, you can request that Moqups permanently delete all applicable data records, including your profile information, both personal and financial, along with any user-created content. In some cases, we may need to retain partial information to fulfil our legal responsibilities, or to complete ongoing financial transactions.

### Data Portability

You have the right, at any time, to request and receive the information that you have provided to Moqups. We will provide you with your information, in a machine-readable format, so that you can make use of it in other contexts, or with other service providers.

### Access Under 16 Years of Age

Moqups’ services are not directed at children. Furthermore, we do not knowingly collect personal information from individuals under 16 years of age, unless consent is given or authorised by the holder of parental responsibility over the child. If we become aware that someone under 16 has provided us with personal details, we will take steps to delete such information. If you become aware that a child has unlawfully or unwittingly provided us with personal data, please contact our Support team.

### Request That We Stop Using Your Information

Even if you have previously consented to our Terms of Service and Privacy Policy, you have the right, at any time, to change your mind and object to the collection, use, and processing of your personal information. Additionally, you are under no contractual obligation to continue to provide any information to Moqups. However, we require certain information in order to provide you with our services. Therefore, if you disagree with the terms of this Privacy Policy or our Terms of Service, you should stop using Moqups, and contact us so that we may delete your information.

List of data sub-processors
---------------------------

| Entity Name | Data Processing Purpose | Location | Website |
| --- | --- | --- | --- |
| Zendesk, Inc. | Customer Support | USA | [https://www.zendesk.com/](https://www.zendesk.com/) |
| REFINER SAS | Customer Surveys | France | [https://refiner.io/](https://refiner.io/) |
| Amplitude, Inc. | Analytics | USA | [https://www.amplitude.com/](https://www.amplitude.com/) |
| Google, Inc. | Analytics, Online Advertising, Cloud Drive Integration, Authentication Provider | USA | [https://www.google.com/](https://www.google.com/) |
| Dropbox, Inc. | Cloud Drive | USA | [https://dropbox.com](https://dropbox.com/) |
| Box, Inc. | Cloud Drive | USA | [https://www.box.com/](https://www.box.com/) |
| Facebook, Inc. | Online Advertising, Social Media | USA | [https://facebook.com](https://facebook.com/) |
| Sentry by Functional Software, Inc | Error Logging and Tracking | USA | [https://sentry.io](https://sentry.io/) |
| Amazon.com, Inc. | Cloud Storage Services, Cloud Email Sending Services, Cloud Infrastructure Provider | USA | [https://aws.amazon.com/](https://aws.amazon.com/) |
| KeyCDN by proinity LLC | Cloud Storage Services | USA | [https://www.keycdn.com/](https://www.keycdn.com/) |
| Slack by Slack Technologies, Inc. | Authentication Provider, Service Integration | USA | [https://slack.com/](https://slack.com/) |
| Mailgun Technologies, Inc. | Cloud Email Service | USA | [https://www.mailgun.com/](https://www.mailgun.com/) |
| PayPal, Inc. | Payment Processor | USA | [http://paypal.com/](http://paypal.com/) |
| MaxMind, Inc | IP Geo Location | USA | [https://www.maxmind.com/](https://www.maxmind.com/) |
| Atlassian, Inc | Enterprise Collaboration | USA | [https://www.atlassian.com/](https://www.atlassian.com/) |

Contacting Moqups
-----------------

If you have any questions about Moqups’ Privacy Policy, or want to make a request with regard to your information, please contact our Data Protection Officer at [dpo@moqups.com](mailto:dpo@moqups.com)

> S.C. Evercoder Software S.R.L.

> Str. Dimitrie Cantemir nr. 5

> Cluj-Napoca, Cluj

> Romania

* MOQUPS

* TEMPLATES

* RESOURCES

* SUPPORT

© 2024 - S.C Evercoder Software S.R.L.

English [Deutsch](https://moqups.com/de/privacy/) [Italiano](https://moqups.com/it/privacy/) [Español](https://moqups.com/es/privacy/)
